question_data = [{"category": "General Knowledge",
                  "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
                  "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered "
                              "together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "One of Donald Trump&#039;s 2016 Presidential Campaign "
                              "promises was to build a border wall between the United States and Mexico.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with "
                              "French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health "
                              "risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
